Supervised machine learning often begins with two major problem types: regression and classification.
Regression predicts a numeric value.
Examples include predicting a house price, sales amount, temperature, or hospital length of stay.
Classification predicts a category or class.
Examples include yes or no, fraud or not fraud, or one of several diagnosis categories.
Both problem types use features, targets, training data, fitted models, and evaluation.
What changes is the type of target, the algorithms we may choose, and the metrics used for evaluation.
In this module, we first used linear regression to connect algebra with learning.
Now we will move into binary classification using logistic regression, where the target has two values:
responded or did not respond.